Assassin's Creed was a very innovative game came out in 2007 it spawned a huge fan base and many sequels
But [what] did it really revolutionize and what can the newer games learn from the old one well?
I have no idea. [I] I don't know honestly I'm going to talk about something completely different now
Assassin's Creed is a game where you play as an assassin during the crusades [as] I have a master's degree in [history]
I feel like I should explain what the crusades were in
1095 Pope Urban II was done in the shower then he had a brilliant idea
[so] he rushed out to his pope board of directors you guys ever heard of Jerusalem. Yeah? Yeah, well it should be our
rusul Em and so they went to war and that's pretty much all you need to know about that the game actually starts with a
Plot twist [you] are really a guy named desmond in the future now today everyone knows this obviously, but back in
Everyone also knew it because the bloody game reviews wouldn't stop spoiling it eight years
Still not over game trailers [Desmond] is being forced into this thing called [the] animus by these two fellows
You use it to sort of travel back in time. Well, you don't really child back in time
You access your ancestors memory, so no hitler killing here, but now finally you get to start the [game]
No
not really because there's a tutorial this tutorial takes ten minutes should take five minutes and
literally feels like six months
Literally, so we finally get to start our game. This is our main character. His name is all [Thai] air
He's with these two dudes now cave, and they have something that needs to be collected
But altair doesn't seem to want to follow the rules
[I] know this because this guy keeps saying hey, you're not following the roads out [there] and altair is acting like a cool kid
So he says wow you're such a loser. [I] do whatever I want and after I'm done with this mission
I'm gonna go smoking with cigarettes. I stole from my mom you can understand that yes
They [are] not going to finish this mission
They see the thing they won't but these [Frenchie's] are in the way all there is of course an assassin
So he thinks up a clever way sneaking up to the templars to then take them out
but then [he] thinks what would an 80s action hero do so instead he walks up to the Frenchman and
Delivers a one-liner blood goes [on] from his terrible, then there's another tutorial because yes
So all day returns back to [Messiah] to speak with the leader of the Assassin Al Mualim
He says tell me about your mission [Al] tears like wait stop
You know what I'm tired of [altair] having an American accent so for the purpose of this video?
I'm going to give him an accent to the mission
I went to shake then the guy from the cave shows up
And he tells mualim about all tears bullshit he also has the thing that they were supposed to get things become really
Awkward just uncomfortable
tension in the room
But all there gets lucky
Because the french are attacking so you go [out] and fight some templars and here's where you learn something new about this game that [you]
Didn't know before is that the combat is incredibly easy?
Silly easy we have on top this platform?
and then there's a cutscene where we get to see some banter between our leader and the
Templar leader give me the thing you stole old man. Come at me, bro
We will take over the land and we will change the laws and you will give us nothing
Do you think we care about loss we don't even care about the laws of Physics [oh]?
Yeah, well
You're a bit of a cunt ah you said wait what all very smart [all] but one of the assassins broke their legs
So they put him out with misery anyways only runs away
And then he cuts this thing open
And then some logs show up and take out the templars
Then they're back at base camp talking al mualim is happy that all pairs solve the whole templar problems with the logs
But you know it wouldn't actually have happened if all they hadn't completely fucked up the mission so they kinda still need to talk about
It so al Mualim is like listen [altair]. We have contacted the Assassin Hr. Department
We have concluded that you can't get fired for this because it didn't have any dramatic effect on our stocks
Well that's great, but we all going [down] to stab you. Oh shit shouldn't have broken the rules
How has anyone told you you're a bit of [a] can boom cliffhanger?
We don't know what happened to altair so you're back at this place
Then you walk around some then you go back into the machine you wake up in Al Mualim's office
The Assassin have resurrected you even though you were dead, but they've also stripped of all your stuff and titles and Etc
so now you have to prove yourself and move up the ranks by
Assassin thingies and now comes the third tutorial this series will go on forever
So you better learn this shit now after you learn how to find and assassinate someone the game actually starts?
[Kassadin] screen ['candy] repeats itself over and over again get a Target
Travel to city of Target Search City to find Target kill Target get new ability your first Target is tamir
He's a black market dealer the bad kind
Not kind of like John you know who gives you half a gram for free if you tell him it's your birthday
Now the bad thing about [today]. Is that he's kind of mean [to] his employees
You kill him in broad daylight, and he's like what the fuck [or] kill Joe might you remain two employees
So I kill joe you kill me because I was mean to my employees hey, hey, maybe contact the Health & Safety
Administration you fucking asshole whenever you kill a target you have to leave the [animus] which is kind of annoying
You play as Desmond provide he walks around he talks to people back in 2007 [this] was okay, because there was like a mystery
But who are these people who kidnap Desmond, but you know today?
We know all this we know that these guys are templars
And they are actually the good guys and we all love them and the assassins that worship
We're supposed to be the good guys are actually just a bunch of whining teenagers for killing Tamir you get throwing knives to
through annoying
Noop quest right to a cray find crazy [Dr.]. [knife] [cray] kill crazy doctor
- I agree might and every time you kill a templar, they will tell you no
I'm actually the good guy every one of them the next target is a slaver named talal
He kidnapped and enslaved people, and he still does it sure I might enslave and torture children
But I heard you assassins. Don't even recycle
We only have one earth. You know [gang] goes on like this. Here's your Target
[thanks]. Oh my way. What bits of account you kill the target so it would appear that you have killed me
But [the] yoke is actually on you as I am not a bad guy
[hahaha]
ending spoilers in bounds
So you've killed the 9 templars and finally you get to face the leader
This guy was his name is so if I'd like 40 guys
Like I said combat is really easy in this game [austere] could probably take on an entire Roman legion with just a very short comb
Then you kill him and he's like
Oh you think that you have beaten the templars, but alas I was not leader
[oh], then this might come as a surprise [to] you, but the actual leader of the templars is Al mualim
Let's most boys at all. He's a beta Lactone. Tevan oh, my Mike
[I] know what you mean
That was the only thing I could think of when I was speaking to him wow this guy is
Such a bit of a cunt. [I] guess we have a lot in common. [no]. I feel like shit for killing
[yeah], don't tell [telemon] you [find] the thing is sometimes you're flush
Sometimes you're bust and when you're up it never feels that you that it seems
And when you're down you think you'll never get back up again, but life goes on good boy, my friend
So you go back to Assassin Hq and Al Mualim has started a cult or something. [I] have no idea. What's going on anymore?
I'm not paying attention at all he freezes you with his super powers then he says
Altair I was actually will the entire time you are weak and stupid. What will I do with you?
oh
I know he summons all the people that you have assassinated before
he does this because they all have the same Ai as normal soldiers so they don't actually clash with each other [you] kill them [and]
Then you get to face him with his teleport ability that he has now
Actually when I say now I'm not sure I mean now because sure the game makes it seems that when he got this apple thing
Suddenly he got superpowers
But they never actually say that [I'd] lied
It's very possible that he had these
superpowers before and that's had them the entire game because out there doesn't seem very surprised at all by these things [you] kill him and
He's like impossible. How can you do this you are, but the studio. I am the master of the response listen or move [aalam]
I've been on this journey for a while now, and I've come to realize something
You're not a bit of [a] cunt. You're a massive cunt [a] giga can't
Account Asaurus rex if you will then [he's] finally dead and you become desmond then you can walk around this office and see symbols they
Predict that the next game is going to be
fucking amazing
That's about it to be honest
there are some unlockables if you finish the game in less than [ten] hours like I did you get the
Black Assassin suit and you get different suits based on the time you finish them, but yeah, that's about it
If you're interested in this game
You should probably check out another review
And that's the [kilian] experience if you like the view you can like it on YouTube
How lovely anyways next year it would probably be bioshock. Yeah, keep it with the 2007 theme after that
I don't know you can request anything you want in the comments also subscribe. I need salad